<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrea Agnolin</title>
    <link>https://agno94.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrea Agnolin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:21:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://agno94.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://agno94.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:21:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agno94.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Math Master thesis: Optimization/Operations research [text] [code repository] Software &amp;amp; utils Freetime (mostly-alone):&#xA;2020 - [Paused] Buonacaccia.net Telegram Bot which used to use webscraping to help italian scout find and get notified about events, currently no longer working 2023-25 - A series of tools to manage and automate financial tracking and reporting for my scout group (some examples: [1] [2]) 2024 - ZFS Home Encryption + PAM unlocker at login + TPM unlock for root [repository] Freetime (mostly-teamworks):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free time</title>
      <link>https://agno94.github.io/free-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:21:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agno94.github.io/free-time/</guid>
      <description>Scout I spend a lot of time as a scout leader (volunteer) for the local group of AGESCI.&#xA;I joined the Scout Movement as a teenager and I&amp;rsquo;ve been a scout leader since end of 2015.&#xA;I think the ideas of Baden Powell (as they are implemented in Italy, at least) are an effective way to train boys and girls in many aspects of life.&#xA;No one can pass through life, any more than he can pass through a bit of country, without leaving tracks behind, and those tracks may often be helpful to those coming after him in finding their way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal CV</title>
      <link>https://agno94.github.io/web-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:03:56 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agno94.github.io/web-cv/</guid>
      <description>Andrea Agnolin&amp;rsquo;s short web version resumé Updated fall 2025&#xA;Education Master Sc. degree in Mathematics at Università degli Studi di Padova, 2021, 108/110, Padua(IT) Erasmus exchange at Universität Bayreuth, 2018, Bayreuth(DE) Bachelor Sc. degree in Mathematics at Università degli Studi di Padova Scuola Galileiana di Studi Superiori in Padua, first 2 years of university Liceo &amp;ldquo;F. Corradini&amp;rdquo; high school, Thiene(IT) High School Awards at Italian national level of Math, Physics and Infomatics Olimpiads Work Experience Quantitive Analyst and Full-Stack developer at Phinergy 2021-2025+ We mainly develop SaaS integrated webapps for business customers in the energy sector.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
